Wait a moment before you write it
This is manually written by us
All the projects we've completed are stored locally.
These kinds of really dazzling effects
like such micro-scenes
There are many online platforms available to create
For example, let's talk about something
mention a platform
Yes, it's called YiQiXiu, YiQiXiu
Look, there's an H5 production
but there are many
Uh, what's MOGARA?
Anyway, there are so many iH5 platforms.
There are many, you know
It's all about H5 production.
that H5 we're talking about, can you code H5?
just this thing
Then let me tell you about a platform
relatively more commonly used
And it's also a free platform, you see.
We can see a platform called YiQiXiu.
Now click to enter, see?
Click on it
added to the official website below
This is the effect he has. Look, all of this is his style.
Let's not look for something so flashy.
Let's go find free templates
Click in
Note that I'm clicking above
Am I clicking on the official website for beauty templates?
See
I'm looking for a beauty template.
For example, what are you looking to do?
Are you making cards?
or an About for enrollment
Yibao, have you seen these things and so on?
Then what you're making is just one UGC Anime after another
right
Let others see it too
Well, last year it was that little yellow bike.
Did they create a version for the Little Yellow Bike?
I wonder if any of you have seen it before.
that is about riding a shared bike
There was one where we created an effect like this
I wonder if any of you have seen this
Here you need to select a free template
We can choose one
for example, Easy Guarantee
You see, activities like golden egg smashing and scratch cards can all be done.
you know
There are also some registrations
some About sections
or product ordering
or any major promotional events
You know, they would create this kind of promotional page.
educational institutions
You see, etc.
Ah, for example, kindergartens and elementary schools.
Adult education is quite popular.
Adult education take a look
After selecting this position
Next, oops
It's a bit laggy
Below is the template section.
Below are the templates.
There are free ones
You see, there are paid VIP options
There's a free version.
You can choose this one, see?
For example, I just don't want to pay
I can choose the free version
Then it will show you all the free options.
You know, like adult education and stuff like that, hey.
Investment and franchise, whatever
Just click any one
For example, click on this one
Hmm, uh, which account am I using?
It shouldn't be this account, right?
It should be this account, forgot
What is this green pepper
Never thought
Oh my god
It's too serious
You just drag it over
Just grab the templates directly
Drag it out, there are templates.
For the captcha, just drag and drop the template directly and take it.
No need to write it yourself
Drag and drop is an attribute in JS.
The code block isn't even encapsulated.
Native JS has the drag-and-drop functionality.
Get the mouse position
and then drag it
Keyboard press, um
Good morning, that pretty girl just disappeared
He's gone after boarding.
Then I'll just pick one randomly
Is this okay?
Xiaoyi Institute of Technology
This thing feels just like making a PowerPoint presentation, you know?
You just feel wow, so awesome
this feeling
And after it's done, this thing is online
can be directly published
Unlike ours
Ours can be written more flexibly after it's done.
But what do we do after finishing writing it?
That thing also needs to be, uh, published to the server.
you know
everyone can use it
You know
This thing is essentially you utilizing someone else's third-party platform
You know what I mean, right?
You're using someone else's third-party platform
but in the end,
there will be an advertisement
If you haven't seen what I mentioned
You must have seen this when a friend got married.
the little wedding thing they sent you
You know what
Wedding season, right?
Yes, yes, yes
or like or something
That is also done using the platform.
After you use the platform
At the end, there will actually be the platform's logo or a like button.
You might click on the platform when you click down
That's what it means.
This kind of stuff
as long as you don't pay
It will always have this logo.
The final bottle, you know what I mean?
If your company does a lot of this kind of promotional work
then your company might purchase this product
That's spending money.
you know
is to purchase a membership for this platform
for example, several thousand or tens of thousands of yuan a year
You know
You can use it for free by recharging like this
they won't display their own official logo
Get it? That's what it means, right?
They definitely need to make money, right?
Right?
Such a platform
Okay now
As I just said, it's just like making a PowerPoint.
You see, there are images here
components can be selected
For example, this logo
Look, we can delete it.
Don't delete it
Hey, look at this spot, something pops up when I click here, right?
See, adjust the size
What position or something like that?
angle and so on
Hey, I can do that too.
upload our own images here
Got it?
Oh, you can do it too.
upload what images
For example, you can upload local images.
Got it? You can upload and do it.
That's what it means
This is my previous one
You can go ahead and upload stuff
That's what it means
You can, for example, upload it.
Then it will take the image from this certain position of yours
That's what it means, just like that.
Ah, you just need to upload a picture.
Then you can just put stuff here
etc.
Just drag and drop stuff here
That's what it means
All of these are defined by the template
Ah, you can add it, okay
This is, like, the template here, you see.
This is the first screen
Can you see the second and third screens?
Do you understand? That is, how many there are
So we can delete it
No need for that.
For example, let's say I just want to make a few pages.
I don't want it
just don't want it
for enrollment
Recruitment
such as kindergarten enrollment or something like that
Adult education or corporate recruitment, etc.
Anyway, it's something people find useful.
How come there are so many?
There are so many bottles, right?
Many bottles
That's what it means
For example, a school introduction
draw a picture
right
Change to another picture
And there are effects here as well.
Let's see where we can check the effect
Let me see
Hmm, I see it doesn't have any special effects.
Let me preview the effect first
Above, you can see there's a save and a preview option
See it
Let me check if the preview has any special effects
It
I click on preview
Ah, it has a page-flipping effect, right?
There is no effect in here.
Actually, the one we found isn't very good.
Because there are so many
For example, I'm now adding this as a child
Let me add an effect
add an effect
Oh, this isn't an effect
This is the color, right?
I should add an animation effect to it.
This is not UGC Anime
Where to add interaction interaction
Click here to open
No no no, sigh
Oh, why is it so confusing now?
It was very simple before.
It looks like a special effect.
container style
This is not a special effect
Let me take another look
This is not an effect
Shouldn't it be a UGC Anime?
Oh, let's see
Select it
This is all about layout.
Is there anything on the left side here?
There's no single-page text material component, huh?
No effects are added.
Interaction is not effect
Advanced no, this is not it
Let me try another version
Let me see if there's any effect.
Can I take a look at it
Let me preview this with a different version.
Let me preview first to see if there's any UGC Anime.
Take a look
How did it switch to this mode?
It turned into a page-flipping effect.
Swipe it quickly
Preview it
This feels right
Do you get that feeling?
Go
Mom and Dad, don't panic
Too fast, too fast
Can you see it?
This is UGC Anime
See, wait
These animations definitely have UGC Anime.
That template might not be very good.
Well then we click, see what this is
See it?
Or you need to click on something inside here
Take a look
Where is the UGC Anime? Here it is.
See? UGC Anime.
how it appears
Can you see it?
See?
It's just whichever one you chose.
It means you don't need to write code, you see
It feels just like making a PowerPoint, you know.
There is also a delay time
See when it appears
Ah, for example, when adults go to work or something like that.
Then it bounces to the right like this
See?
Hey, you can add time, got it?
That's what it means
Then you go ahead and do it
or let you now, ah, build upon the original foundation, ah
On top of his original foundation, you can proceed to work.
You can see there are many layers
See?
It feels just like making a PowerPoint, you know.
Okay, after finishing it up,
After finishing, we need to preview it first
or click Save
you know
Finally, for example, you can use a template
then delete all those images
discard
you know
Then fill in your pictures
You know
It feels just like making a PowerPoint.
And finally, this thing here
Take a look at its cover
You can change the cover.
Select from your local files or elsewhere
for example, Me pictures
Choose a cover ah
Just choose any randomly
Select a cover image
Change it
For example, confirm that the cover is uploaded
See
The cover is now uploaded.
And here is its title
This is the title
Only the title you send to others can be displayed
And here is the description of the article.
There's also music at the end
See
There's no sound in this part
You'll hear the sound when you watch it later
Just pick one that's visible, ah ah
Then the preview mode of the work is from top to bottom.
Let's not worry about this.
Then the work will be displayed on the Home.
It doesn't matter
Ahem, then there's the background settings and the background.
Is this background a solid color or something else?
We don't need to care about the layers.
For example, we've finished writing it
Just save it after writing.
or preview it first
Do you understand?
You can make changes one by one after you're done editing.
That's what it means
It's a large long image
It's not page by page.
If it's page by page
It would be more convenient for you to view
It's equivalent to putting all the layers together, right?
Didn't we just see them page by page?
page by page
There is a layer.
this thing
For example, when I finish writing
I have also previewed it
I think it looks good
then I save it
After saving
I want to publish it now
You don't publish
Only visible on your personal account
We just click publish
We click publish.
It can be seen by everyone
That's what it means, right?
Just take your URL
At this moment
it will generate a QR code and a link for you
Just scan the QR code with your phone to view it
you know
That means you can see it, right?
Then you can also
Ah
You'll see the same effect when you open it
That's what I mean, do you get it?
Ah, it's also this effect, just a free generated one.
Ah, a generated thing.
Well, I can also take a look at the works inside.
Me to-do list
Me
Just pick any one
Look, it's like this.
For example, editing a work, you go ahead and find one
You have to look for it
I won't go through each one for everyone.
a bit laggy
See, it's page by page.
Can you see it?
Is this what you mean?
Page by page, ah
Ah, each page
For example, when I click here
There's animation here, can you understand?
Yeah, that's what it means.
Ah, there's UGC Anime.
Then move it
for example, the UGC Anime of which character
Got it
You get the idea
Just like making a PowerPoint
There's nothing to it.
you really encounter it
You click it
Just click and you'll get it.
Got it?
You'll get the hang of it in no time.
We have hosted this platform.
Finally, look at the fence
Oh my, surrounded
There is an advertisement
Did you see the webpage?
We have to pay to remove it.
See? That's your ad
You can't delete it
Do you get what I mean?
Well, you need to pay for it, right?
Otherwise, if you use someone else's platform, it's bound to include their branding, right?
That's how it is.
Unless you have a corporate account
The enterprise account has paid for it.
not required
If your business frequently uses it
would opt to pay
If your company only occasionally does a one-time promotion
they won't pay for it either
Just go with it, just go with it
Is that what you mean?
Yeah, that's what it means.
If you were to create this kind of H5
You can choose to use this platform to write what you want
send to the backend server
Then you just follow the approach we used earlier, got it?
the approach we just used
previously, some students wrote
that is the content we previously explained using swap
Got it
the content explained using swap
Then someone sent him an effect
said just let you write this effect
The original version was written in swap.
you know
You can take a look and study it.
can write it out
It basically involves mostly images.
you know
then give you a URL
Please refer to this effect
Just write this effect
You've already sent the URL
You can definitely see it
You know
If it's online
just for some promotion
nor does it require your server or anything like that
you know
This kind of thing can be generated online right away.
Just use this platform.
Got it, right?
Of course, there are some other platforms as well.
Let's not talk about this.
Okay, got it.
That's all.